Finding Aid for Department of Recreational Sports (University of Michigan) publications, 1976-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Department of Recreational Sports (University of Michigan) publications 1976-2000
University of Michigan. Department of Recreational Sports
0.5 linear feet
97144 Bimu 2
Publications of the Department of Recreational Sports at the University of Michigan, includes annual reports, pamphlets and brochures, calendars, manuals such as the Recreational Sports Program and Policy Guide, and schedules such as the Recreational Drop-In Schedule. Also contains manuals from the intramural sports program.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Publications are received periodically from the unit (donor # 8287 ).
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open without restriction.
Please consult the history found in the finding aid for Department of Recreational Sports (University of Michigan) records.
The PDepartment of Recreational Sports publications (.5 linear foot) includes annual reports, pamphlets and brochures, calendars, manuals such as the Recreational Sports Program and Policy Guide, and schedules such as the Recreational Drop-In Schedule. Also included manuals from the intramural sports program. Thue Pubications are organized into two two series: Unit Publications and Sub-Unit Publications.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Dept. of Recreational Sports.; University of Michigan--Sports.; University of Michigan. Athletic Dept.; Intramural sports--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Recreational drop-in schedule.; Recreational sports program and policy guide.
Genre Terms:
Annual reports.; Pamphlets.; Calendars.; Manuals.; Schedules (time plans)
- Unit Publications
  The Unit Publications subseries includes annual reports covering the years 1976 through 1977 and 1985 through 1991, brochures, and calendars. Manuals under various titles such as Intramural and Recreational Sports Handbook (1974-1975), Recreational Sports Program and Policy (1978-1979), and Recreational Sports Program and Policy Guide (scattered issues from 1980 to 1992) date from 1974 to 1992. They describe the various programs within and the policies of the department. Schedules for the recreational drop-in programs cover the period from 1977 to 1995.
  - Annual Reports
    - 1976-1977 (Box 1)
    - 1985-1991, 6 folders (Box 1)
  - Brochures, 1974-1979 and undated (Box 1)
  - Calendars
    - Recreational Sports Activities Calendar, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - Manuals
    - Intramural and Recreational Sports for Men and Women, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
    - Intramural and Recreational Sports Handbook, 1975-1975 (Box 1)
    - Recreational Sports Handbook, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Recreational Sports Program and Policy Guide
      - 1980-1981 (Box 1)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 1)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 1)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 1)
    - Self-Directed Fitness, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Schedules
    - Recreational Drop-In Schedule, 1977-1995 (Box 1)
- Sub-Unit Publications
  The Sub-Unit Publications subseries includes brochures, calendars, manuals, and schedules describing programs within the department. These include the Challenge Program, the Intramural Program, and the Outdoor Recreation Center.
  - Challenge Program
    - Brochures
      - Challenge, undated (Box 1)
  - Intramural Program
    - Calendars
      - Intramural Calendar of Events, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Manuals
      - Intramural Sports Handbook, 1932/1933 1963/1964 1965/1966-1968/1969 and undated (Box 1)
      - Intramural Sports Manager's Manual, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters
      - The IM newsletter, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Rosters
      - Hockey, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Outdoor Recreation Center
    - Brochures, undated (Box 1)
    - Calendars
      - Outdoor Recreation Schedule of Events, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
    - Manuals
      - Canoeing and Camping: Guide to Southeastern Michigan, undated (Box 1)
    - Schedules
      - Rentals, 1985 and 1987-1991 (Box 1)
      - Schedule of Events, 1991-1996 (Box 1)